Get out.
Get out!
I'm on a hot surface!
[CAR DOOR OPENS]
Are you crazy?
[CAR DOOR CLOSES]
Yes.
Living a hard life
makes me crazy.
Let's stop fighting!
I have a proposal.
Be my Papa Ping.
We'll share the inheritance.
Right?
That's a win-win situation.
[PLAYFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
Come on.
[SMACK]
[BLOWS]
[SILLY SFX PLAYING]
- [GLASS BREAKS SFX PLAYING]
- Agh! Ouch!
- [STOMPING]
- Ouch! My heart!
Hey, chill out!
Think about it.
Give me a month.
Just a month.
A month.
You'll be a nuisance
for a month.
I've got tons to do
in the mansion.
I'm not going to bother you.
And when the month is over,
and you still don't want me,
fine, whatever.
What now?
Come on.
[ZIA] Uh...
this could be the answer to
your problem with your brother.
Our firm is building
an estafa case against Toto.
And the share offered by June
will be more than enough
to make up
for Pindang Tocino's loss.
I can't trust her, Attorney.
Just because
your brother deceived you
doesn't mean
everyone will do so.
I know it's hard to trust again.
But... try.
[PING]
My brother will never learn
if I just keep saving him
over and over.
I can't just spend the money
I didn't work hard for.
Is there no other way?
Unless she's not related
by blood, which she is.
We checked.
All her records are clean.
[PING] And all the inheritance
would just go to this scammer?
I won't make it easy for you.
Watch your back.
Okay.
Fine!
One month.
[TAPS] There we go!
[SCOFFS]
To think you were acting
all shy earlier. [TONGUE CLICKS]
See? You didn't have
to make a fuss.
I'll make sure you fall in love
with me within a month.
I'll also find proof that
you're not related to Don Nato.
[ELECTRICITY CRACKLING
SFX PLAYING]
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]